<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2023-10-20T13:37:08.450+11:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="admin"
        cq:template="/conf/w-recipes/settings/wcm/templates/page-content"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Chicken, Brocolli &amp; Cheese Bake"
        sling:resourceType="w-recipes/components/page">
        <root
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="w-recipes/components/container"
            layout="responsiveGrid">
            <container
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="w-recipes/components/container"
                layout="responsiveGrid">
                <title
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="w-recipes/components/title"/>
                <container
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="w-recipes/components/container"
                    layout="responsiveGrid">
                    <contentfragment
                        jcr:created="{Date}2023-10-20T13:37:08.406+11:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="admin"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2023-10-20T13:37:08.406+11:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="w-recipes/components/contentfragment"
                        displayMode="multi"
                        fragmentPath="/content/dam/w-recipes/recipes/non-vegetarian/chicken,-broccoli-&amp;-cheese-bake"
                        text="Chicken, Broccoli &amp; Cheese Bake Title Chicken, Broccoli &amp; Cheese Bake Main Image /content/dam/w-recipes/recipes/images/chickenbroccolibake.webp Prep 15 Cook 25 Serves 4 Difficulty 3 Steps Preheat oven to 200°C. Cook broccoli in a saucepan of boiling water for 2 minutes or until just tender. Drain. Remove meat from chicken and roughly chop. Discard skin and bones. Heat cream cheese, milk and mustard in a saucepan over medium heat, stirring until smooth. Remove from heat and add 1/2 cup cheese, stirring until melted and combined. Squeeze liquid from spinach. Combine chicken, broccoli, sauce and spinach in an 8-cup capacity ovenproof dish. Combine breadcrumbs, butter and remaining cheese in a small bowl. Sprinkle over chicken mixture. Bake for 20 minutes or until the crumb topping is golden and the bake is heated through. Serve with salad if desired. Ingredients 20g butter, melted 20 grams butter, melted 1 1/2 cup milk 1 and 1 half cup milk 250g frozen chopped spinach, thawed 250 grams frozen chopped spinach, thawed 1 large head broccoli, cut into florets 1 large free-range BBQ roast chicken 1 large free-range BBQ roast chicken 250g light cream cheese 1 tbs dijon mustard 1 tablespoon dijon mustard 4 cups garden salad (optional, to serve) 4 cups garden salad (optional, to serve) 1/2 cup panko breadcrumbs 1 half cup panko breadcrumbs 3/4 cup tasty cheese, shredded 3 quarters cup tasty cheese, shredded Step 1 Preheat oven to 200°C. Cook broccoli in a saucepan of boiling water for 2 minutes or until just tender. Drain. Step 2 Remove meat from chicken and roughly chop. Discard skin and bones. Step 3 Heat cream cheese, milk and mustard in a saucepan over medium heat, stirring until smooth. Remove from heat and add 1/2 cup cheese, stirring until melted and combined. Squeeze liquid from spinach. Combine chicken, broccoli, sauce and spinach in an 8-cup capacity ovenproof dish. Step 4 Combine breadcrumbs, butter and remaining cheese in a small bowl. Sprinkle over chicken mixture. Bake for 20 minutes or until the crumb topping is golden and the bake is heated through. Serve with salad if desired. Categories woolworths:recipes/allergies/egg-free woolworths:recipes/allergies/peanut-free woolworths:recipes/allergies/sesame-free woolworths:recipes/allergies/tree-nut-free woolworths:recipes/category woolworths:recipes/category/fresh-ideas woolworths:recipes/course woolworths:recipes/course/main woolworths:recipes/cusine woolworths:recipes/cusine/australian woolworths:recipes/vegetables woolworths:recipes/vegetables/spinach"/>
                </container>
            </container>
        </root>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
